Privacy Policy
==============

Effective Date: December 26, 2025

This privacy policy outlines what information we collect, how we secure it, and how we use it in relation to the service illumin provides to its customers via our advertising technology platform.

### Who we are

illumin (“we” “our”) is a leading advertising company that provides a technology platform (the “Platform”) for marketers, offering a powerful and holistic solution for digital advertising across all ad formats and devices to amplify reach and Share of Attention™ throughout the customer journey. illumin has developed a proprietary technology platform that enables marketers and agencies to effectively target consumers with digital advertising. Most of the internet is offered to users free of charge. Web publishers are able to offer valuable content for free because they are supported by advertising. illumin aims to create a better digital experience for web users by allowing advertisers to present relevant advertising content, rather than advertising that is unrelated to users’ interests. Advertisers also benefit because targeted advertising is more effective and better received.

We offer this privacy policy (the “Policy”) because we take your privacy seriously. This Policy outlines our privacy practices with respect to the illumin Platform. If you want to understand illumin’s privacy practices with respect to our corporate website and information we collect from our customers, please visit our [Corporate Privacy Policy](https://illumin.com/legal/corporate/).

We are members in good standing with the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI), and participants in the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) and the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada’s (DAAC) Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioural Advertising. We continuously improve our privacy safeguards in order to help protect information about your browsing activities.

Overview of the types of data collected by illumin’s Platform

#### Personal data

The definitions of personal data vary depending on the laws where you are located. For example, in the European Union (EU), Canada and in certain U.S. states such as California, personal data is defined more broadly than in other places and would include both identifiable personal data (“PII”) (e.g., email addresses and phone numbers) and Pseudonymous Identifiers (defined below). Some places use the term “personal data” while other places use the term “personal information”. illumin will explain the different types of personal data and personal information below, and will try to be clear when we’re describing our use of each throughout this Policy. illumin does not knowingly place PII on our advertising Platform, but we do process Pseudonymous Identifiers via the Platform.

#### Pseudonymous identifiers

illumin collects or otherwise processes Pseudonymous Identifiers via the Platform. Pseudonymous Identifiers help our Platform recognize a particular browser or device, but do not enable us to know your identity as a natural person. This information helps us collect and make use of other personal data to better understand your interests and preferences. The pseudonymous identifiers processed via the Platform include Google Advertising ID, Apple Identifier for Advertisers, hashed email addresses, illumin ID and IP address.

#### Privacy practices for our technology platform

The illumin Platform processes data collected across non-affiliated websites and mobile applications pursuant to serving advertisements on behalf of our Clients who are generally businesses seeking to market a product or service. We obtain this information from website and mobile application publishers, connected television devices, advertising exchanges, supply side platforms and other companies which help illumin place bids on ad slots on behalf of our advertisers. We obtain information using one or more of the following tracking techniques or technologies, which are all widely used across the Internet.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small data file stored on your device. In the context of our Platform the illumin cookie often contains a Pseudonymous Identifier that is assigned to your browser the first time it is seen by our Platform. On subsequent interactions with our Platform, we use this Pseudonymous Identifier to, among other things, recognize what advertisements your browser has interacted with previously. Our cookies are not used to identify you personally, cannot be used to install malware, viruses or any other harmful software and they cannot access any confidential data on your computer. For more information about cookies in general, please visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org/](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

#### Pixels

Pixels (also known as web beacons) are tiny images embedded in a web page that allow our Platform to infer that you’ve seen on that web page. They also allow us to create, update and read our own cookies.

#### Advertising IDs

An Advertising ID (device identification) is another Pseudonymous Identifier associated with a smartphone or similar handheld device. Advertising IDs are accessible by mobile application publishers and can be passed to illumin with an ad request. These Advertising IDs do not enable illumin to identify individuals, but rather can be used to help us run advertising campaigns. They can be used to limit the number of times a specific advertisement is presented to the same device, and to track a device to show that the device interacted with an ad (i.e. “clicked” on it, watched a video ad, or downloaded an application as a result of an advertisement).

#### ID-Synching/Cookie Synching

We engage in cookie syncing of Pseudonymous Identifiers via the Platform in order to match our IDs with those of third-party partners.

### The information we collect via the Platform

Using the technologies described above, we collect and use Pseudonymous Identifiers. Pseudonymous Identifiers do not allow us to identify you personally. Their primary use for illumin is to help us managing our Client’s advertising campaigns, serve users more relevant ads, count the number of ads served and to understand how you and other Internet users interact with ads. This information is collected when you visit the website or mobile application where one of our ads are served. The Platform collects information about your browser type, operating system, device, and the unique identifier assigned to your device. Demographic data such as age range, income level or gender may be collected. In addition, we collect information about your web browsing and app usage, such as the date and time you visited one of our partner’s websites or apps, pages of such websites or apps that you visit, the names or types of mobile apps that you visit, and other data such as page visits, ads shown, ads clicked and conversions over multiple non-affiliated websites and mobile apps for the purpose of creating interest segments to tailor advertising and content is sometimes referred to as “Interest Based Advertising” or “IBA.” We engage in IBA via the Platform. Where we are able to infer within a reasonable probability that a particular computer or device belongs to the same user or household as another computer or device, we may link those computers and/or devices with each other. Where we are able to make such inferences, we may use this information to deliver targeted ads across multiple computers or devices. This is sometimes referred to as cross-device advertising, and we generally don’t conduct cross-device advertising on computers or devices located in the EU. We also use other targeting techniques such as leveraging data received by Clients once it is rendered pseudonymous via a privacy-safe third-party service provider. Some of the transfers of Pseudonymous Identifiers and other pseudonymous information from The Platform over the past 12 months may be considered a sale under applicable law, and we provide a mechanism that enables you to opt-out from such sales, profiling, automated decision-making and interest-based advertising activities engaged in by our Platform and pursuant to our Client’s advertising campaigns. Note: The categories of data we process via the Platform under CCPA includes (a) Personal and Online Identifiers such as: IP address, mobile advertising IDs and similar pseudonymous UIDs and (b) Internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing history, and information regarding a consumer’s interaction with an internet website application, or advertisement.

We do not use the Platform to collect PII such as your name, postal address, phone number, or email address. However, we may receive hashed email addresses for use on the Platform. And we don’t collect sensitive information such as social security number or credit card number via the Platform. The data we collect is primarily used to understand your online activity and consequentially provide you with relevant advertisements based on the websites you’ve visited, mobile applications you’ve used and similar data provided by our Clients and third-party data partners.

The information we collect is used to deliver personalized advertisements and to measure the effectiveness of the ads.

illumin may also collect data that can be used by our Clients and partners and receive certain data from Clients and partners. This data may include whether or not you have visited our Client’s website and/or mobile app, or if you have used a website and/or app that our Client advertises on. The data collected is used to build a consumer profile. We use the data (including the data used to create profiles) in our algorithm to better understand your interactions online and to pair the right advertisements with the right consumers. With this information we can deliver you more personalized advertisements targeted to your interests. In some places, this process is considered an automated decision.

### Potentially sensitive information pertaining to children and health conditions

illumin does not intentionally or knowingly collect information from children under 18 years of age, and does not tailor any segments to children under 18 years of age.

### Data retention

illumin retains the web log data for a maximum of 180 days, although we generally don’t retain this data for EU data subjects for more than a few days. After 180 days, we aggregate the log data so that it does not identify any individual device and retain the aggregate data for up to three years. Our cookies are set to expire before one year; this expiration date updates every time you encounter our server.

### Security

illumin takes reasonable measures to help protect the information we collect from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. This includes but is not limited to the use of firewalls and encryption. No method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure; therefore, while the company strives to use commercially acceptable means to protect your information, it cannot guarantee absolute security.

### Choice mechanism: objecting to processing, profiling, opting out, do not sell, or share my info

Many Internet users enjoy receiving relevant advertisements. Our algorithm reads your online data and aims to deliver you the most relevant advertising content available. This results in you only seeing ads that match your inferred interests. Without targeted advertising, marketers do not know your consumer preferences and will likely deliver you ads that you are uninterested in.

It is also important to consider that the websites you use receive substantial payments from marketers to present interest-based ads. These increased revenues can improve website content and pass on a reciprocal benefit to you, as the user. Without these revenue websites are more likely to deliver lesser value content. illumin periodically evaluates the benefits of our profiling and the targeted ads served by our platform against the potential risks to data protection rights.

### Browser-based choice mechanisms

If you prefer not to receive targeted advertising from illumin, you can object to our processing of browser data by the Platform by clicking [here](https://illumin.com/legal/opt-out/), by visiting the NAI website [here](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!%2F), by going to the DAA website [here](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN) or the DAAC website [here](https://youradchoices.ca/en/tools). Data subjects may also opt-out of profiling and automated decision-making by the Platform as well as the automated decision-making, sale, or sharing of their personal information where required under applicable law by clicking the above links. If you opt-out, we will set a cookie on your browser that tells illumin not to tailor ads to your interests – including any profiling, sale, sharing, targeted adverting, IBA and cross-device ads. Opting out does not mean you will not be served an ad by illumin, but the ads we serve will be less relevant to your interests. Please note that the opt-out cookie only applies to the computer and browser where it is set. Also, if you delete the opt-out cookie (such as by clearing all cookies on your browser), you will need to renew your opt-out choice. EU data subjects receive additional rights as described below. Also, where we receive a request to opt-out of profiling or sale/sharing of personal information from a publisher or SSP, we will treat that user has having opted-out of our systems.

To better understand the process of behavioral advertising, please visit:

*   Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) – [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)
*   Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) – [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/)
*   Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada (“DAAC”) – [youradchoices.ca](http://www.youradchoices.ca/)

Finally, you may control and/or opt-out from the use of certain targeted advertising, ad targeting profiling and sale/share of information related third-party pixels on this Website by clicking on the “Cookie” icon that is placed on the lower corner of your screen while you visit this Website. Clicking on the icon will access the Website’s consent management platform (CMP) which will allow you to make privacy choices related to the Website.

### Mobile choice mechanism

Opting out on a mobile device:

If you are using a mobile device and would like to opt-out, then please follow this [link](http://www.networkadvertising.org/mobile-choice) for instructions on how to opt out across multiple mobile operating systems such as iOS and Android. Please note that the opt-out process is different for each mobile operating system. The presence of an opt-out tells illumin not to tailor ads to your interests – including any profiling, sale, sharing, targeted adverting, IBA and cross-device ads.

Opting out does not mean you will not be served an ad by illumin. Rather, if we do serve you an ad once you’ve opted-out, the ads we serve will be less relevant to your interests. EU data subjects receive additional rights as described below.

### Disclosure, onward transfer

We contract with a select group of third-party processors and service providers such as networking and storage providers to allow them to carry out their services for us. Other third-party service providers used by illumin include: a) outsourced computer programmers helping ensure our systems are operating properly; b) email marketing providers, c) website and b2b sales analytics providers, d) customer relationship management, contact database vendors, data hygiene vendors, survey vendors and project management software providers, e) customer billing systems partners, f) login authentication providers to ensure that the logins to our systems are working efficiently, g) social media platforms for advertising and marketing purposes, h) auditing, debugging and security vendors. Those processors and service providers are contractually obligated to process data only as instructed by illumin.

Please take note of the following exceptional situations: illumin may be required to disclose information to third parties when obligated to do so by law and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected, or actual prohibited activities, including transfer reasonably intended to meet national security or law enforcement requirements, or when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, including but not limited to fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person. In the event that illumin sells, merges or transfers all or part of its business, we may transfer visitor information to a third party as part of that transaction.

### Do Not Track

A number of industry groups are attempting to develop a Do Not Track (DNT) standard. Currently, the standards regarding the DNT signals and appropriate responses are not consistently defined. Where we can ascertain that a browser being used by data subject has enacted DNT, and that data subject is located in a place where adherence to DNT or similar opt-out preference signals is required, we treat that data subject’s browser or device as having opted out from illumin’s profiling, ad targeting, automated decision-making, and sale/sharing of their personal information as described in the section of this privacy policy covering privacy choices.

### Accessing, changing, removing information

We adhere to applicable laws when it comes to honoring data subject rights such as access, deletion and correction with respect to the Platform. If you’re located in the EU, UK, Switzerland or certain U.S. States, scroll down to see any the data subject access rights which are available to you with respect to the illumin Platform.

### U.S. data subjects

Certain U.S. states (e.g., California, Colorado, Connecticut, Delaware, Indiana, Kentucky, Iowa, Maryland, Minnesota, Montana, Nebraska, New Hampshire, New Jersey, Oregon, Rhode Island, Tennessee, Texas, Utah, and Virginia) provide additional privacy protections for their data subjects under applicable law, including: a) the right to see what data we have about you, (i.e., the right to know), b) the right to delete the data we have about you, (i.e., the right to delete), c) the right to correct the data we have about you, and; d) the right to opt-out of the sale of data about you (i.e., the right to opt-out from sales of your information). Most of these rights are also applicable to the Pseudonymous Identifiers and other personal data collected about your computer or device by the Platform. We do not discriminate against you if you exercise any of the above rights. Moreover, we may not be able to honor a right if doing so would violate applicable law.

You may access those rights with respect to illumin by sending us an email to [privacy@illumin.com](mailto:privacy@illumin.com), by calling our California privacy help line at 1-866-6Acuity, or by visiting our [data subject access page here](https://illumin.com/legal/subject-access-request/). If you make a subject access request as set out in this policy, you are entitled to see and delete the personal information that we have about you. We will confirm your request within 10 days and make a good faith attempt to fulfill your request within 45 days unless applicable law provides that we do so more quickly. Some jurisdictions provide you with the right lodge an appeal to illumin if you are unsatisfied with our response to your request to exercise the rights above. Please send any appeals to [privacy@illumin.com](mailto:privacy@illumin.com) Some U.S. states also provide you with the right to further appeal our determination to a consumer protection agency located in that state. For example:

*   Colorado – [The Colorado Attorney General’s Office](https://coag.gov/office-sections/consumer-protection/)
*   Maryland – [Maryland Attorney General Consumer Protection Division](https://www.marylandattorneygeneral.gov/Pages/CPD/default.aspx)
*   Nebraska – [Nebraska Attorney General’s Office](https://ago.nebraska.gov/)
*   New Hampshire – [Data Privacy Unit of the Consumer Protection and Antitrust Bureau of the New Hampshire Attorney General’s Office](https://www.doj.nh.gov/news-and-media/attorney-general-formella-announces-creation-new-data-privacy-unit)
*   New Jersey – [Division of Consumer Affairs in the Department of Law and Public Safety of New Jersey](https://www.njconsumeraffairs.gov/)
*   Texas – For denied appeals, visit the [Texas Attorney General’s Office, Consumer Protection Division](https://www.texasattorneygeneral.gov/consumer-protection/file-consumer-complaint)
*   Virginia – For denied appeals, visit the V[irginia Attorney General’s Office, Consumer Protection Division](https://www.oag.state.va.us/consumer-protection/files/tips-and-info/Virginia-Consumer-Data-Protection-Act-Summary-2-2-23.pdf)

The number of CCPA requests to know that illumin received, compiled with whole or part and denied in 2024: 11, 11 and 0.

The number of CCPA requests to delete that illumin received, compiled with whole or part and denied in 2024: 194, 194 and 0.

The number of CCPA requests to opt-out that illumin received (not including requests made via illumin’s cookie based opt-out mechanism) compiled with whole or part and denied in 2024: 401, 401 and 0.

The median number of days within which illumin substantively responded to requests to know, requests to delete and requests to opt-out: 1, 1 and 2.

### European Union, Swiss and UK data subjects

The General Data Privacy Regulation (“GDPR”) affords additional rights to EU data subjects. Switzerland and the United Kingdom have similar data protection laws in place which grant similar rights. When this policy references EU data subjects, we also mean to include data subjects located in all of the EEA as well as Switzerland and the UK. Those rights include the right to complain to Supervisory Authorities and the right to access, correct, opt-out, and delete certain personal data processed by illumin. In certain circumstances, a consent is required (e.g., prior to the placement of a cookie by our Platform).

As described above, with respect to EU data subjects, personal data includes Pseudonymous Identifiers such as an IP address, a mobile advertising ID, a hashed email address or a cookie ID. Where illumin is a controller of data (e.g. via our Platform), the legal basis will be consent in accordance with Article 6 of the GDPR and depending on the type of information subject to processing and the information we receive from upstream partners. To the extent that we may rely upon legitimate interest for further processing, we have assessed the processing is not high risk and will not violate fundamental human rights. For example, we may process [TC Strings](https://usercentrics.com/knowledge-hub/iab-tcf-2-2-transparency-and-consent-framework-quick-guide/) for the purpose of ensuring and being able to demonstrate that Users have consented to or not objected to the processing of their personal data in connection with targeted ads on our advertising Platform. We process personal data of Clients and partners for the performance of our contracts with them in accordance with Article 6 of the GDPR.

Where illumin receives from an EU data subject a request to cease processing of data via one of the choice mechanisms listed above, illumin will stop all data processing with respect to the opted out browser or device unless such processing is required by law.

If you believe illumin is processing one of your Pseudonymous Identifiers and wish to exercise your right to access, delete, port or remove such information, please click [here](https://illumin.com/legal/subject-access-request/) to visit our EU & U.S. data subject access request page.

For all requests concerning the security of your data, please contact our Data Protection Officer at [dpo@illumin.com](mailto:dpo@illumin.com).

If you have a particularly sensitive request, you may want to consider contacting our Data Protection Officer by postal mail, as communication by e-mail can always be flawed by security vulnerabilities.

### Revisions

illumin reserves the right to revise its policies and practices periodically. If you would like to keep up to date, please visit this page to find out about any changes. We will post any updates as well as their effective dates on this webpage.

### Appendix

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about our privacy policy or data protection, please contact us:

illumin Inc.  
70 University Ave, Suite 1200  
Toronto, ON, Canada  
M5J 2M4  
(416) 218-9888

The illumin Data Protection Officer is Alan Chapell and he may be reached at [dpo@illumin.com](mailto:dpo@illumin.com).

The illumin EU Representative is Josep Tribo and he may be reached at [representative@illumin.com](mailto:representative@illumin.com).
